<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Create, make, break.</title>
    <link>http://albertlatham.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Create, make, break.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://albertlatham.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Goodbye 2018</title>
      <link>http://albertlatham.com/post/goodbye-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://albertlatham.com/post/goodbye-2018/</guid>
      <description>Great things that happened this year.  I got to see family for almost an entire month. I did well in Spring, Summer, and Fall sessions of school. I learned that it is ok to feel bad, alone, sick. I (re)learned that God does His work even when I don&amp;rsquo;t feel or see anything. I worked a couple of interesting jobs (barista, vehicle lift maint./installer). I changed my degree path to computer science!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modeling a Corner Bracket</title>
      <link>http://albertlatham.com/post/i3-printer-modifications/modeling-a-corner-bracket/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://albertlatham.com/post/i3-printer-modifications/modeling-a-corner-bracket/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR - I modeled a corner bracket using Blender in a somewhat parametric manner. If you want to look at the file and see what I did you can find it here. You can also skip down to the modeling section to see exactly what I did. Recently I replaced my Duplicator&amp;rsquo;s Melzi controller with something a little more sane. I&amp;rsquo;ll write a blog post in the future about the dependancy hell required to actually get a Melzi to work but for now, I need a bigger space to put my Smoothieboard in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Duplicator I3 Auto-Bed Leveling with a Smoothieboard.</title>
      <link>http://albertlatham.com/post/i3-printer-modifications/adding-auto-bed-leveling/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://albertlatham.com/post/i3-printer-modifications/adding-auto-bed-leveling/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for the video, Thomas. I found this video quite a while ago and I decided I&amp;rsquo;d give auto bed-tramming (bed-leveling) a go.
  Final battle with a Melzi. A cursory glance at the Melzi&amp;rsquo;s page on the Reprap website will only begin to illuminate the issues one will face if they attempt to modify the firmware on board in any manner. The Duplicator I3&amp;rsquo;s controller ships with Repetier which didn&amp;rsquo;t support any sort of auto bed-leveling at the time I tried to make this work.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>